{
      "questions2": [
{
    "id": 1,
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "Which hackers are considered hostile?.",
    "answer": ["Black-hat", "Cracker"],
    "choices": ["White-hat", "Black-hat", "Gray-hat", "Cracker"],
    "feedback": "White-hat hackers are professionals who hack with authorization in order to identify weaknesses in a program. A black-hat hacker hacks to break IT security and gain access to systems without authorization for their own purposes. A gray-hat hacker contains average abilities who can probably be a black-hat or white-hat hacker in the future. A cracker possesses sophisticated skills and are the biggest threats for networks and resources.",
  },
{
      "id": 2,
      "type": "MC",
      "question": "What are the tenets of information systems security??", 
      "answer": "All of the above",
      "choices": ["Confidentiality", "Integrity", "Availability", "All of the above"],
      "feedback": "Confidentiality is when only authorized users can view information. Integrity is when only authorized users can change information. Availability is when information is accessible by authorized users when they request for such information. All these components are essential and are all classified as tenets of information systems security." 
  },
{ 
      "id": 3,
      "type": "multi_text",
      "questionOne": "RPO stands for ",
      "questionTwo": "and RTO stands for ",
      "questionThree": ".",
      "answer": ["Recovery Point Objective", "Recovery Time Objective"],
      "choices": "answer_to_question",
      "choices2": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": "RPO stands for Recovery Point Objective. It is the maximum amount of data loss that is acceptable. RTO stands for Recovery Time Objective. It is the maximum allowable time to recover the function."
  },
{
    "id": 4,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "Which of the following is a type of injection?",
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "choices": ["SQL", "XML", "LDAP", "All of the above"],
    "feedback": "All of these are types of injection techniques that are popular in malware development. SQL injections are used to attack applations using SQL statements. XML injections are used to manipulate the logic of an XML. LDAP injections exploits websites that constructs LDAP based on user input."
  },
{
    "id": 5,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "Which malware uses robots to launch attacks?",
    "answer": "botnets",
    "choices": ["virus", "worm", "botnets", "trojan horse"],
    "feedback": "Botnets are robotically controlled networks created by hacking groups (bot-herders) to attack vulnerable machines."
  },
{
    "id": 6,
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "Which domains don't experience unauthorized access as a common threat?",
    "answer": ["User", "WAN"],
    "choices": ["User", "Workstation", "LAN", "LAN-to-WAN", "WAN", "Remote Access", "System/Application"],
    "feedback": "User domains and WAN domains can't be breached through unauthorized access since WANs are accessible to most users and user domains can be breached."
  },
{
    "id": 7,
    "type": "MC",
    "question": "A plan that contains the actions needed to keep critical business processes running after a disruption is called ___.",
    "answer": "Business Continuity Plan (BCP)",
    "choices": ["Disaster Recovery Plan (DRP)", "Business Impact Analysis (BIA)", "Business Continuity Plan (BCP)", "none of the above"],
    "feedback": "Business Continuity Plans are plans that handles how to deal with outages in IT systems, applications, and data and continue business operations."
},
{ 
      "id": 8,
      "type": "multi_text",
      "questionOne": "The two main types of malware are ",
      "questionTwo": "and ",
      "questionThree": ".",
      "answer": ["viruses", "worms"],
      "choices": "answer_to_question",
      "choices2": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": "Malware exists in two main categories: infecting and hiding programs. Malware of this type includes viruses and worms."
  },
{ 
      "id": 9,
      "type": "multi_text",
      "question": "A honeypot is a sacrificial host with deliberately insecure services deployed at the edges of a network to act as bait for potential hacking attacks.",
      "answer": "true",
      "choices": ["true", "false"],
      "feedback": "Malware exists in two main categories: infecting and hiding programs. Malware of this type includes viruses and worms."
  },
 {
    "id": 10,
    "type": "checkbox",
    "question": "Which U.S. compliance laws for information security systems were passed in 2002?",
    "answer": ["Federal Information Security Management Act (FISMA)", "Sarbanes-Oxley Act (SOX)"], 
    "choices": ["Federal Information Security Management Act (FISMA)", "Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA)", "Children's Internet Protection Act (CIPA)", "Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA)", "Sarbanes-Oxley Act (SOX)"],
    "feedback": "FISMA & SOX were passed in 2002, but they updated FISMA in 2014 with the \"Federal Information Security Modernization Act\". CIPA was passed in 2000 and was updated in 2011. GLBA was passed in 1999 and HIPAA was passed in 1996." 
  },
 {
    "id": 11,
    "type": "true_false",
    "question": "Cryptography is the practice of hiding information.",
    "answer": "true",
    "choices": ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": "Cryptography is often used in businesses for personal transactions since it has the ability to hide user information like their credit card information to keep their information secure from outside sources."
  },
{
    "id": 12,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What does EULA stand for?",
    "answer" : "End User License Agreement",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question",
    "feedback": "EULA stands for End User License Agreement. These are typically what you see before you register for a service which contains the license agreements between a user and vendor."
},
{
    "id": 13,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What does HTTP stand for?:",
    "answer" : "Hypertext Transfer Protocol",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question",
    "feedback": "HTTP stands for Hypertext Transfer Protocol. It is the communication protocol between web browsers and websites that contains data in cleartext."
},
{
    "id": 14,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What TCP/UDP port number does HTTP have? (type only the number)",
    "answer" : "80",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question",
    "feedback": "HTTP belongs in port 80 of the application."
},
{
    "id": 15,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "What does DDoS stand for?",
    "answer" : "Distributed Denial of Service",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question",
    "feedback": "DDoS stands for Distributed Denial of Service, which is when someone floods a network with malicious data to the point where the network can't function properly. (So if you're playing a game with a network server and experience heavy network issues or lag, there might be a slight chance you're being DDoSed)."
},
{
    "id": 16,
    "type" : "MC",
    "question" : "Which of the following are challenges to access controls?",
    "answer" : "all of the above",
    "choices" : ["laptop loss", "exploiting hardware/applications", "eavesdropping", "all of the above"],
    "feedback": "All of these choices can compromise access controls. Laptops are a physical access control that can affect the owner if they lose it. Exploiting hardware/applications are logical access controls that can be compromised by hostile users. Eavesdroping can also affect logical access controls (i.e. when someone overhears another give out classified information like passwords, etc)."
},
{
    "id": 17,
    "type" : "text",
    "question" : "__ is a program/hardware device that inspects network traffic and has the ability to permit/deny trafic based on the configuration rules.",
    "answer" : "Firewalls",
    "choices" : "answer_to_question",
    "feedback": "Firewalls serves the purpose to inspecting network traffic and are known to be effective countermeasures to network threats."
},
{
    "id": 18,
    "type" : "true_false",
    "question" : "The Internet is an open, public network shared by the entire planet. Anyone can connect to the Internet with a computer and a valid Internet connection and browser.",
    "answer" : "true",
    "choices" : ["true", "false"],
    "feedback": "The Internet is accessible to anyone who can connect to the network."
},
{ 
      "id": 19,
      "type": "multi_text",
      "questionOne": "The two types of access controls are ",
      "questionTwo": "and ",
      "questionThree": ".",
      "answer": ["Physical", "Logical"],
      "choices": "answer_to_question",
      "choices2": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": "Physical access controls are physical resources like buildings, parking lots, and protected areas. Logical access controls are components of a computer system/network like usernames, and passwords."
  },
{ 
      "id": 20,
      "type": "multi_text",
      "questionOne": "LAN stands for ",
      "questionTwo": ". WAN stands for ",
      "questionThree": ".",
      "answer": ["Local Area Network", "Wide Area Network"],
      "choices": "answer_to_question",
      "choices2": "answer_to_question",
      "feedback": "LAN stands for Local Area Network. LANs are a collection of computers that are conncected to one another. WAN stands for Wide Area Network. WANs are networks that extends over a large geographic area, connecting multiple LANs."
  }
 ]
}
